[
  {
    "type": "intro",
    "pretext": "You’re halfway through your katakana lessons! Awesome! Take this short quiz and see how much you’ve learned. But first, let's review:"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "G",
    "options": ["Ga – ガ", "Gi – ギ", "Gu – グ", "Ge – ゲ", "Go – ゴ"]
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Z",
    "options": ["Za – ザ", "Ji – ジ", "Zu – ズ", "Ze – ゼ", "Zo – ゾ"]
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "D",
    "options": ["Da – ダ", "Dji – ヂ", "Du – ヅ", "De – デ", "Do – ド"]
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Do",
    "options": ["ダ", "ド", "ヂ", "ヅ"],
    "answer": "ド"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Zo",
    "options": ["ザ", "ジ", "ズ", "ゾ"],
    "answer": "ゾ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Da",
    "options": ["ド", "ヂ", "ダ", "ヅ"],
    "answer": "ダ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Gi",
    "options": ["ギ", "ド", "ダ", "デ"],
    "answer": "ギ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Ji",
    "options": ["ゾ", "ジ", "ザ", "ゼ"],
    "answer": "ジ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Du",
    "options": ["ヂ", "ダ", "ヅ", "ド"],
    "answer": "ヅ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Dji",
    "options": ["ヂ", "ド", "ダ", "ヅ"],
    "answer": "ヂ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Ga",
    "options": ["ド", "ガ", "デ", "ヂ"],
    "answer": "ガ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Ze",
    "options": ["ゾ", "ザ", "ジ", "ゼ"],
    "answer": "ゼ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "De",
    "options": ["ド", "ダ", "デ", "ヅ"],
    "answer": "デ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Za",
    "options": ["ガ", "ゾ", "ザ", "ゼ"],
    "answer": "ザ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Zu",
    "options": ["ゾ", "ズ", "ジ", "ゼ"],
    "answer": "ズ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Go",
    "options": ["ゲ", "ガ", "ギ", "ゴ"],
    "answer": "ゴ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Gu",
    "options": ["ゴ", "ガ", "ギ", "グ"],
    "answer": "グ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Ge",
    "options": ["ガ", "ギ", "ゲ", "ゴ"],
    "answer": "ゲ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Denwa",
    "options": ["デンワ", "ナカマ", "カゾク"],
    "answer": "デンワ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Kazoku",
    "options": ["デンワ", "カゾク", "シロイ"],
    "answer": "カゾク"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Gakusei",
    "options": ["ヒラガナ", "ガクセイ", "カタカナ"],
    "answer": "ガクセイ"
  }
]